

CONTACT

- Málaga, España
- +34697883410
- fcojnavarrowork@gmail.com

SKILLS

TEAMWORK

LEADERSHIP

CODE REVIEW

BEST PRACTICES

RESPONSIVE DESIGN

CONTROL VERSION

CI/CD

NEW TECHNOLOGIES

MOBILE DEVELOPMENT

LANGUAGES

English

Intermediate

Spanish

Native

FranciscoNavarro

Front End Web Developer

PROFILE

Front-End Web Developer with 4 years of experience specializing in React, Angular and Ionic frameworks. I stand out for my ability to work in a team, as well as for my experience in leading and mentoring other developers. Committed to creating efficient and attractive user interfaces, I bring innovative solutions and a collaborative approach to every project.

EXPERIENCE

Front End Web Developer

(\) 11/2023 - 07/2024

☐ ESAIL IT SOLUTIONS ⊙ Málaga, España

At ESAIL I led the Front End team, where I improved organization and productivity by introducing key methodologies and technologies. I focused on ensuring code quality through thorough reviews and the application of best practices, continuously monitoring to maintain high standards in each project.

Front End Developer

(\) 05/2023 - 11/2023

At KUBIDE, I contributed to the development of Front-End solutions, ensuring best practices, performance optimization, and usability. I took on responsibilities in training colleagues, quality control of the code, and project management from the outset to ensure their success.

Front End Web Developer

() 01/2020 - 08/2023

■ ESAIL IT SOLUTIONS ⊙ Málaga, España

At ESAIL, I focused on the analysis, organization, and development of innovative products, managed the Front-End team, and trained new department members. I also ensured best practices, implemented methodologies and technologies, and maintained communication with clients to provide customized solutions. Additionally, I prepared documentation and user manuals with the final product.

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Full Stack Web Development

(\) 10/2020 - 10/2021

☐ CodeHouse Academy ⊙ Málaga, España

Telecommunications Engineering

(\) 10/2013 - Present

□ University of Malaga (UMA) ⊙ Málaga, España